Hi! I'm Emily. Nice to meet you.

I'm a graphic designer and visual thinker, who strives to create and develop playful, engaging, interactive solutions. An ambitious and quick learner with boundless imagination, I am always excited to take on the next challenge, and to explore its creative possibilities. With over five years of experience designing for a variety of industries, including healthcare, theater, finance, e-commerce, and non-profit organizations, I've honed my ability to adapt my design aesthetic to a range of brands and styles.

experience

Isobar

Visual Designer | New York, NY | Jan 2015 - August 2016 Designing digital experiences, including responsive websites, iOS and Android apps for TV, tablet, and mobile, portal applicationsmobile apps, presentations, and case studies. Conducting marketing research for pitches. Providing creative QA of products in development. Clients include NBC (USA, Bravo, Syfy, Telemundo, E!, Esquire, NBC Universo, Oxygen, Sprout, MSNBC), IntegraMed, LexMar Global, and Umpqua Bank.

Situation Interactive

Interactive Designer | New York, NY | May 2013 - Aug 2014 Concepted and designed websites, landing pages, flash and static banners, rich media units, social media assets, and digital campaigns. Storyboarded and video edited. Provided creative direction to freelance designers and creative QA. Clients included The Metropolitan Opera, Roundabout Theatre, Ripley's Believe It or Not!, and Broadway musicals Wicked, Cinderella, Rock of Ages, Mama Mia!, Beautiful, Hedwig and the Angry Inch, Of Mice and Men, If/Then, and The Bridges of Madison County.

GAIN Capital

Interactive Designer | Bedminster, NJ | Jun 2012 - May 2013 Concepted and designed online and print branding materials for FOREX.com and GAIN Capital Holdings, including flash banners, landing pages, e-mail, widgets, infographics, social media, and style guides. Managed the frontend development of landing pages. Co-branded the Tradable appstore. Oversaw the development of the new TradeKing Forex microsite. Customized TradeKing trading platforms and mobile apps.

Zemoga

Graphic Design Intern | New York, NY | Jun 2011 - Aug 2011 Concepted and designed brand materials including a laptop case, notepads, coffee packaging, the Pixels & Pills blog and YouTube assets.

DoSomething.org

Graphic Design Intern | New York, NY | Jan 2011 - Apr 2011 Designed wireframes, landing pages, and web and print collateral for campaigns including the "Stop Bullying" campaign, Aeropostale's "Teens for Jeans," HP's "Green Your School Challenge," VH1's "Battle for the Bands." Created branding system for DoSomething.org's program BootCampX.

Nimli

Graphic Design Intern | New York, NY | Nov 2009 - Feb 2010 Designed banners and hero images. Retouched product photos for website.

education

Pratt Institute

New York, NY M.S. Communications Design, Digital Design Emphasis Honored as Distinguished Student May 2012

Carnegie Mellon University

Pittsburgh, PA B.H.A. Creative and Professional Writing & Art, with Honors, Minor in Business Administration May 2009

skills

Art Direction, Branding, Illustration, Interactive, Motion, Packaging, Photography, Print

Software

Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Sketch, AfterEffects Flash. FinalCut Pro, Dreamweaver

Web Design

Knowledgable in HTML, CSS, JQuery

Language

English (native) Mandarin Chinese (fluent) Spanish (basic)

honors

Hilson Family Scholarship Award for Excellence, 2011 American Assocation of Advertising Agencies Award, Operation Jumpstart Scholarship III Recipient, 2010 - 2011 National Honors Scholar Society, 2009 Dean's List, 2008 - 2009